Zed Poirier

121 Blucher Street, Kitchener, ON Cell: (226) 755-1020 Zed.Poirier@gmail.com

SUMMARY

My skillset focuses on creating engaging, immersive experiences by using iterative design principles, low-detail 3D modelling, and efficient scripting techniques for quick prototyping.

- VR & Mobile Development
- Rapid Gameplay Prototyping
- Technical Art Focus
- Bilingual (English & French)

SKILLS

- Languages & Engines: C#, Unity, Python, HLSL, Godot, HTML, CSS
- 3D Software: Blender, Maya, 3DS MAX, Substance Painter, Materialize
- Multimedia Tools: Adobe Suite, OBS, Google Docs
- Production Tools: Jira, Trello, GitHub, SVN, Google Drive, Slack, Discord

EXPERIENCE

3D Digital Artist - April 2019 to Present

VARLab - Kitchener, ON

- Customized and tailored demos to meet the needs of the end client
- Developed and integrated digital assets for virtual reality training simulations
- Researched techniques to improve efficiency of asset creation and demo performance

Game Master - August 2018 to January 2019

MirageVR - Kitchener, ON

- Maintained a calm control over large groups around our high-end technology
- Troubleshot technical errors during setup and mid-game to ensure a smooth experience

Customer Service Guru - Sept 2016 to April 2018

Shopify Inc. - Kitchener, ON

- Solved clients' technical issues over phones, chats, and emails
- Coordinated with multiple teams simultaneously to speed up resolutions

EDUCATION

Game Design Diploma

- Sept 2018 to present
- Conestoga College, Kitchener, ON

Broadcast Television Diploma

- Sept 2013 to April 2014
- Conestoga College, Kitchener, ON

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

• Gamemaster in roleplaying games such as D&D, Savage Worlds, and Blades in the Dark